Pranav Paranjape

QA automation/manual lead - Python, selenium, robot framework

pranav.paranjape@gmail.com

Summary

Experienced Testing professional with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry.

Skilled in Agile Testing, Test complete, Python, HP QuickTest Professional (QTP), Requirements Analysis, Agile Methodologies, and Test Automation. Strong quality assurance professional with a BE focused in Mechanical from Goa Engineering College.

Experience

QA Automation Lead at Qualys July 2018 - Present

Principal Quality Engineer at Nuance Communications

February 2017 - July 2018 (1 year 6 months)

working as a principal QA engineer. Manual as well as automation activities.

Specialist-Testing at FIS

September 2009 - February 2017 (7 years 6 months)

Asst. Systems Engineer at Tata Consultancy Services

November 2007 - September 2009 (1 year 11 months)

Quality Engineer at Approva

May 2005 - October 2007 (2 years 6 months)

Education

Goa Engineering College BE, Mechanical, 2000 - 2004 Deepvihar High school 10th, Schooling, 1988 - 1998

Pranav Paranjape

QA automation/manual lead - Python, selenium, robot framework

pranav.paranjape@gmail.com



Contact Pranav on LinkedIn